I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
Let's start getting back to our hotel.
You're right. This place
looks kinda dangerous.
Say, look!
That dog...
Yeah! It looks just like Ryusuke-kun's dog!
-Hey! Let's get a picture!
-Yeah!
It's coming this way!
-I'm scared!
-Kii-chan, watch out!
-He's gonna maul us to death!
-Yo! Keith!
Keith, what's the matter with you, man!
Getting all bloodied and chasing chicks
up and down the street, man!
Just gotta be careful with women!
We're in trouble!
"Broadcast in the School"
And then?
They took all our money, of course!
And we walked back to the hotel.
It was a miracle we made it home!
I'll say!
And this is the dog's photo.
Imagine, coming across a dog
that looks like Beck.
So blurry I can't make any sense of it!
Huh? Oh, come on!
I'm going to the convenience store
to get toshikoshi noodles.
-We really saw it!
-Yeah!
Well, anyway, at least you're okay.
Oww! Hot!
I pray that Hyodo's not in my class!
"Fortune"
"Temporary danger
followed by peace of mind."
Yes!
"March"
"In Jamaica until the 20th"
The old lady went to Jamaica this time?
(Graduation Song)
Today, you graduate
from East Ihara Middle School.
"Graduation"
Today, you graduate
from East Ihara Middle School.
Use what you have learned at
this school to move to the next level.
And please remember, you are not alone...
Izumi-chan...
Hurry!
Sorry! Sorry!
Izumi-chan!
Hey, what's with your melon roll?!
Hyodo!
The sugar coating's all melted!
This isn't a melon roll!
Sorry. The usual bakery was closed...
Huh?! Whatever. Go buy another one.
Okay...
Tanaka-kun!
"Saito Paper Company"
Are you going to your part-time job now?
How do you do?
"Saito Paper Company"
I'm Ogasawara, Tanaka-kun's
substitute homeroom teacher.
You're Saito-san...right?
You can call me Kenichi!
Oh, let me make you some tea!
A part-time job? Don't be silly.
I'm just a crazy middle-aged man
who's teaching Yukio-kun
how to swim and play the guitar for free.
I see. But what a relief.
I'm glad you have such
a good friend, Tanaka-kun!
Koyuki-kun...That Momoko-sensei
is really a nice teacher...
Kenichi Saito, age 44. Very discerning.
Unattached and independent.
I hope everyone here spent
the holiday in a worthwhile manner.
"School Entrance Ceremony"
I hope everyone here spent
the holiday in a worthwhile manner.
"School Entrance Ceremony"
We start a new school year today.
At this time of year...
"Grade 9A"
We start a new school year today.
At this time of year...
I will be the homeroom teacher
for 9th grade, group 1.
My name is Eiji Oikawa. I'm looking
forward to this year with you.
My forte is imitating Mick Jagger.
That's where you laugh.
Hey, Tanaka...He knows.
Someone snitched to Rikiya-kun
that you busted up the Jaguar.
And now I'm tangled up in this.
I see...
Can you get 50,000 yen in three days?
I-I don't think so.
He wants 100,000. I'll get 50,000 somehow.
-You have that much?
-Idiot! I'll get it somehow!
Somehow?
Do something within three days!
I'm serious; it's your fault
if he kills you!
50,000 yen...in three days?
That's impossible...
The White Falcon...
the ultimate Gretsch guitar.
It's the pride and joy of my collection.
I'll let you borrow this, Koyuki-kun.
For as long as you like.
Huh?! Are you serious?!
You always work hard for me.
Saito-san!
And...I've been thinking it'd be nice
to see Momoko-sensei again...
I'm counting on you.
Ryusuke-kun...
Koyuki...
That guitar...
This is a White Falcon.
Oh? It's called the
most beautiful guitar in the world.
Where are you-
I'm going to the studio
for practice. Wanna come?
Yes!
All right, our time is limited.
Let's get started, Koyuki.
Huh? Me too?!
You can play, right?
Thanks for today! See you later!
-He's really been practicing.
-Yeah.
He's far past a first-year beginner.
Yeah, I agree.
And he has a feel for the music.
Hey, Tanaka...
Are you making a fool of me?
That's all I could make from
selling my games and comics!
Do something by tomorrow's deadline.
We're talking about Rikiya-kun here!
Saito-san! Please do something
about this pile of sex magazines!
These magazines are proof
that I've lived through
the Showa and Heisei eras!
But you can't live in the past like this.
Momoko-sensei won't like you...
Let's take these to the dump!
Huh?!
This is that
super-famous star, Miho Nakama!
"Miho Nakama on a tropical island"
This is that
super-famous star, Miho Nakama!
"Miho Nakama on a tropical island"
Koyuki-kun! H-hurry!
"Used Books Store"
W-wow!
46,500 yen? This isn't enough.
I can't get any more.
Shit! It's the deadline,
so I'll give it to Rikiya-kun,
but don't blame me for
whatever happens to you.
Cripes!
-It's Rikiya-sempai!
-What? He already graduated!
Move! You're in the way!
-Yamada! Where the hell is he?
-Hello!
Idiot! Do you know how much
I begged Rikiya-kun, dumbass?
I'm sorry.
Damn right!
Something's not right...
Hold it! Time out!
Koyuki. Listen to the drums.
-Hey, look at those two.
-Huh?
They've been awfully
close lately, those two.
Hey, don't rub it in. This guy
worries more than you think.
By the way, have you heard the New Order?
Huh?
That's why I hate the Japanese!
That kind of thinking
won't get you anywhere!
You're Japanese, Maho!
-Shut up! That doesn't matter!
-What about Do Division?
-Yeah. How about Happy Mondays?
-You can't just say no to everything!
-I'm not saying that!
-Yeah, New Wave, right?
Hey, Koyuki...
-Take this.
-What is it?
Ryusuke-kun! Hey! Wait!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
-What's the matter?
-Nothing...
-Something happen with my brother?
-No, nothing...
"Minami"
What a huge house!
It's not like I built it.
I heard Taira-kun talking about you.
He said, "Koyuki's progress is amazing.
Like cotton absorbing water."
Huh? Was that an impression of Taira-kun?
But everyone's so slow.
I knew you had talent ages ago.
Oh, thanks...
It'll be done copying in a little bit.
Huh? Something wrong?
Err, no...Oh yeah, I gotta
pay you for the minidisc.
-You dropped something.
-Huh?
No, it's not what you-!
Where'd you get that from?!
My head still throbs...
What if I wind up dying?
-There's this movie I wanna see...
-Yes?
Are you free this Sunday?
Oh, that uniform!
-See you tomorrow!
-All right!
Oh, Koyuki! Hiya!
Izumi-chan...Who was that just now?
-An upperclassman in my club.
-Oh, I see...
Is he-?
He said he wants to go out with me.
If I walk around like this in a daze...
life is gonna just pass me by!
Whoa, how awful!
'Morning, Kojima-kun!
About the book I lent you-
Kigata-kun, I was thinking...
Hey, Tanabe...
Yeah, and then...
Hey, shape up!
You asked me for a copy...
"Broadcasting"
"Media Room"
What's that?
-What's this broadcast?
-It's American music.
Yeah...
This song...
Hey, open up!
If you don't open up now,
it'll go on your school record!
Hear that?!
-Huh?! It's Tanaka!
-Tanaka-kun!
Open up!
-Hey, Tanaka!
-Cut this out!
-Tanaka!
-Tanaka-kun!
-Man, it's so loud!
-What a racket!
-But I like this song!
-It's not bad.
This song's pretty good.
Yeah...But man, it's taking you long!
"Faculty Office"
-Now tell me.
-Yes...
"Faculty Office"
Why would an earnest student
like you do such a thing?
-Do you watch movies?
-Not too much. Why?
An innocent man who is
wrongly sent to prison
plays an opera that he loves in prison.
And the rest of the inmates
feel freedom for just a moment.
There was a scene like that.
Huh? This isn't prison!
That was Dying Breed's "50 Cent Wisdom."
That was a great choice!
-Who are you?
-Yuji Sakurai, Grade 9B.
Do you play an instrument, Tanaka-kun?
Sakurai-kun...You probably
shouldn't talk to me.
Huh? Why not?
Someone bad has it in for me...
-Who's that?
-Some weird transfer student.
Hey, transfer student.
Come to the back of the campus.
We'll teach you how things are done
at East Ihara Middle School.
I see. So you're the Hyodo Gang.
The culprits who make life
at school miserable.
You cocky bastard!
Why you-!
Bastard!
Tanaka-kun!
Your face!
I wanted to give this to you.
It's Dying Breed's Germany concert.
Sakurai-kun...
I told you it was bad to talk to me...
Did you read the Eddie Lee
interview in Guitar World?
Yeah. Eddie's Telecaster was cool.
There are two types of people in this world.
Huh?
Clever people and obedient people.
Clever people think man-made laws
and morals make the world work.
But I don't bother with any of that.
Eddie is amazing, huh?
Oww!
Won't you come see
our band practice sometime?
So you're in a band?
Ryusuke said earlier that he wants
to make the band's sound hotter.
He intends to bring Koyuki into Beck...
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
I had such a shock recently.
"Next Episode"
"Eve of the Live Show"
I had such a shock recently.
"Next Episode"
"Eve of the Live Show"
A girl told me...that my feet stink!